Many of us are dealing with the fact that we are becoming clear.
And in that clarity, we are seeing the things that we saw in like film and TV and comic books, et cetera, that seemed like they were just fantastical.
You know, that could never happen in real life.
On levels of supernatural, on levels of moral turpitude, on levels of conspiracy.
We now understand, oh, yeah, those things are real.
They were putting them in these spaces of entertainment to basically like divert us from thinking that they could be real.
And that realization can be incredibly overwhelming.
What I want you to remember, though, is that with all of that, there's another side of that.
Which means that the mysticism, the magic, that is also real.
I'm serious. I believe this.
Like when you would see these shows that are showing like that there's like individuals across the world that possess particular powers that are able to actually challenge the evil that's at play.
You might be like, oh, come on.
Now, you know that you have met some of those people.
You know that you have met people that possess something different.
They possess a connectivity.
They possess an awareness, an acuity.
And if you are not those people, then that means that you are also responsible for protecting them, for nurturing.
We are all a part of that mysticism and magic and bringing it back and enforcing it and encouraging it and cultivating it.
Y'all keep thinking saving us is going to come from voting.
Saving us will start when we move beyond the limitations that were given to us.
You understand it when you look at the works of people like George Orwell.
When you look at the works of Ray Bradbury, when you look at the works of Octavia Butler, you're like, wow, how could they know?
And it's very scary to think, oh my gosh, the evil we've seen in television and film could be real.
Do not get lost in the overwhelm of the darkness because you are actually the descendant of that magic.
And they convinced you that it didn't exist while they used it on you.
Remember, I wrote a whole article that relates to this on Substack.
Go and check it out.
It's part of my new series, Full Moon Musings.
And this installment is the revolution in you.
You're damn rude, eh?